indianastrologysoftware.com 2017-12-02

# Privacy Policy - IndianAstrologySoftware.com

This privacy policy sets out how www.indianastrologysoftware.com uses and protects any information that you give www.indianastrologysoftware.com when you use this website. www.indianastrologysoftware.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

www.indianastrologysoftware.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from November 1, 2008. 

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

We use cookies to deliver various services and to keep track of your personal preferences. A cookie is a small text file that can be entered into the memory of your browser to help a website recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site, allow a site to track usage behavior, compile aggregate data for content improvements and undertake targeted advertising. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers contain a function that allows a user to deny the cookie feature. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our Web site and other Web sites. In the course of serving advertisements, these companies may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your hard drive, and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies, please visit <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> and <https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/>

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site. 

We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.

Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 

Astro-Vision Futuretech Pvt.Ltd.,  
Door No. 31/2165-A3, 1st Floor, White Tower,  
Kuthappadi Road, Thammanam P O,  
Cochin - 682 032, Kerala, India,   
Phone: +91 484 2343925, 3390000,  
E-mail:[cochin@astrovisiononline.com](mailto:cochin@astrovisiononline.com)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

## AstroSuite 2.0

This astrology software suite is a combination of 8 different astrology software products, ideal for business users.

### This Astrology Software Suite Contains:

  * Lifesign 14.0 
  * SoulMate 11.0 
  * GemFinder 11.0 
  * YearGuide 3.0 
  * DigiTell 9.0 
  * Namefinder 1.1 
  * PanchaPakshi 1.0 
  * StarClock VX 2.0

#### English + Malayalam + Tamil + Telugu + Kannada + Hindi + Marathi + Bengali + Sinhala*

*Some software are available in fewer languages.

Get A Quote

## StarClock ME Ultimate

This mobile astrology software includes Horoscope Matching,Prasna, Muhurtha and lots more. Available in Android and Java.

### Key Features: 

  * Multi-lingual interface and reports 
  * Detailed Marriage matching 
  * Calculations and charts for any date and time 
  * Save and retrieve birth data of individuals 
  * PDF conversion of reports 
  * Compatible with all android mobiles

#### English + Hindi + Telugu + Tamil + Marathi + Kannada + Malayalam

*Requires Android 2.2 & above

Get A Quote

## Like us on Facebook

## Follow us on Google+
